♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely?
♪ Lucky there's a family guy
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us
♪ Laugh and cry
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Good evening. I'm Tom
Tucker bringing you news
you heard four hours
ago on the Internet.
Our top story: A mishap
in Quahog harbor today.
That's right, Tom.
A ferry carrying a shipment
of brand-new Mercedes
Benzes from Germany
crashed and sank just
a few miles off our coast.
Thus far, the cars
remain on the ocean floor
as the Germans refuse
to clean up the disaster.
The German
Environmental Minister
called a press
conference to issue
the following statement:
(thick German accent):
I see nothing! I know nothing!
Holy crap! Did you
hear that, Lois?
All them fancy cars out
there in the ocean, just
free for the taking?
I'm gonna get me a Mercedes!
Peter, that may be the
stupidest idea you've ever had.
And you've had some
pretty stupid ones.
Hi there. Peter Griffin.
You know, a lot of us here
at Family Guy are, frankly,
sickened by the sorry state
of education in this country
and how little
you people read anymore.
So, for this next cutaway,
we're gonna make you read it.
That's right, you heard me.
Do a little work
once in a while,
instead of having
everything spoon-fed.
You want your yuks,
put in a little effort.
All right, go ahead.
Okay, that one might
have been more of a visual,
but you feel that feeling
you got right now?
That's satisfaction.
You just read something.
And no one can take
that away from you.
Proud of you.
Geez, you're a mess.
What is that?
It was finger-paint day.
What the hell?
Why didn't they clean
you up before you left?
Brian, there's, like,
37 other kids in there.
One was in a drawer all day.
Wow, seems like Lois would've
checked that stuff out
before sending you.
Yeah, you'd think so, right?
I mean, it's clearly
not a place of business.
It's someone's house.
You know, half the time you
can hear someone showering.
I mean, you never see them, but
you can hear the shower going.
Really? That seems weird.
Yeah, and is it normal
that Miss Emily tied
us all to the sink
while she went out to
return a birthday present?
No, that's not
normal at all.
You know, Stewie,
maybe I should
come by tomorrow
and check things out.
That teacher sounds
really irresponsible.
She is. Adults are stupid.
The world would be so much
better if it were run by babies.
TV ANNOUNCER:
Tonight on NBC... Shapes!
(excited cooing)
And then... Colors!
Followed by
an all-new... Dad's Keys!
(cheering, cooing)
(quiet snoring)
Man, I can't wait
to get a Mercedes.
Me, either.
Yeah, it's gonna be sweet.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa!
What the hell is that?!
A sun hat.
No, no, no, no, no.
What do you mean, no?
I'm protecting my face
and neck from the sun.
Use sunscreen!
Y-You don't need
to put a circus
on your head.
This is a ploy
for attention.
Sunscreens are
bad for you.
The chemicals get
in your skin.
Boy, you really want
to wear that hat.
That hat's coming off!
No!
(grunting)
You guys are jerks!
I can have my own identity
besides you two.
Not this way.
Not the hat way.
Holy crap!
I think we got one!
Aw, damn it!
It's just a dolphin.
(with British accent):
Sorry,
did I get in the way
of something?
No, it's all right.
We were just trying
to get some of them
sunken Mercedes.
Oh, yeah, there's a great big
pile of them down there.
Me and my mates, right,
we was having a laugh
sitting in of one of them,
pretending to be people.
(chuckles)
You know, like, driving around
getting into incidents
with other motorists.
Honk, honk. "Stay out
the way, you old bat!"
Asian.
Not all Asians
are bad drivers.
No, no, not
all terrorists are Arab.
But, you know, they are, so...
Uh, well, I'm Peter,
and that's, uh, Joe,
and that's Quagmire.
Name's Billy, Billy Finn.
It's got "fin" in it.
I didn't pick it.
(chuckles):
Luck of the draw.
Say, you want me to try
and get you one of those cars
from down there, yeah?
(gasps)
You would do that?!
Well, I could try.
Here, let me
give it a go.
He seems nice.
He does.
Yeah.
So, uh, what do you have
planned for the summer?
I'm sure he'll
be right back.
Sorry, mate, all I could get
was this hood ornament.
(gasps)
This is just as good!
Thank you so much!
Hey, you know,
if there's ever anything
I could do for you...
Actually, you could
do something.
You could eat only
dolphin-safe tuna.
Wait, is that the brand
that costs five cents more?
No, I can't do that.
Things ain't so good
in America right now,
which is why
we're all so fat.
What did I tell you, Brian?
It's a nightmare in here.
Oh, my God!
Oh, what happened to that kid?
He fell off a stool
trying to turn off
Maury Povich.
This is awful!
Where's your teacher?
Probably out back.
Excuse me, are you Miss Emily?
Yeah. Hi. Who are you?
Uh, Brian.
Brian Steel.
I was just
dropping Stewie off.
Oh, yeah! I should
probably go back in there,
see how everyone's
doing, I guess.
Ah, they're fine.
In fact, I see Stewie
reading a book.
Scratch-and-sniff
Lindsay Lohan Goes Jogging.
Oh, God! That's terrible!
Oh, here's a pop-up book.
Tommy Lee Goes Boating.
Move, Lois! You're on
the hood ornament's pillow.
Peter, put that away.
It's time for bed.
W-Wait, hang on, Lois,
before I go to bed,
I just got
to do one thing.
Hello?
Hey, Mr. Pewterschmidt,
it's me, Peter.
You remember how you said
I'd never amount to nothing?
Is that a Mercedes?
Peter, hang up the phone.
(doorbell rings)
My God, who could be at
the door at this hour?
I don't know, but this late,
it's got to be bad news.
Everyone knows you
always get bad news
in the middle of the night.
Wake up, wake up, wake up!
Huh? What?
You have cancer!
What?!
Yeah. I thought
you should know.
Okay, go back to sleep.
Wait, I have questions.
(sighs)
It's very late.
Oh, hello. This
is the right house.
(chuckles)
That's good, then.
What the hell?
It's me, Billy. Billy Finn.
Just wanted to take you up
on your nice offer from earlier.
What... I-I don't... What offer?
(snickers)
You know, the bit about
"If there's ever
anything I can do,"
so, yeah...
Oh.
Yeah, thought I might
make a go of it on land.
So, "anything you
can ever do."
Here I am. Thank you.
Squid pro quo.
(chuckles)
Thank you for not
being "shellfish."
(giggles) I just said that
for the "halibut."
(laughs)
Fish puns.
Ah. Oh, cod.
(laughing)
Oh, God, come on.
(grunts)
Let me in.
Peter, who is it?
Is Meg dead?
It's that dolphin--
I think he wants to crash here.
And I have no info on Meg.
He wants to what?
I-I'm not sure that...
I brought a gift.
Put it to your ear.
You can hear the ocean.
♪ Caribbean Queen
♪ Now we're sharing...
It's broken or something.
All I hear is...
It's Billy Ocean!
(cackling)
Oh, God! I got
loads more.
So, Billy, I, uh, I hope
the couch was all right?
Yeah, a lot better
than the floor.
And I should know, 'cause
I went down on the floor,
thinking it had to be a
lot better than the couch.
Okay, well,
breakfast is ready.
Oh. Uh...
Is everything all right?
Yeah. Well, it's just...
would you mind tossing
it up in the air for me?
Well, I don't know...
Lois, he is our guest.
Toss it in the air.
Uh, I'm used to a
little applause, so...
(faint clapping)
All right, all right.
Not bad. Afternoon crowd.
Lightly attended.
So, Billy, how long will
you be staying with us?
Are you kidding?
As long as he wants!
Yay! We live with a dolphin!
Anyway, I'm off
to read Meg's diary.
Only been here one night,
but I get the sense
we all dislike Meg.
Um, I'm a dolphin--
smart, intuitive.
Also, Peter told me
in the hall. Ha.
Peter, I'm not so sure about
Billy staying here with us.
What are you talking about?
He's hilarious.
I don't know.
Listen, just leave it to me.
I'm great with animals.
Remember when I lived
with those ants?
We're working on something.
Yes? May I help you?
Hey, put him down!
Who are you?
I-I can't stop him!
Can anyone stop him?
No? Well, he's gone.
Hey, Stewie.
How's it going?
Brian, what are you doing here?
Came by to check on my pal.
Where's, uh, Miss Emily?
I haven't seen her yet today.
She gave me the keys to open
up when she left yesterday.
I thought you said you
were gonna talk to her.
I did, a-and she's doing
her best, you know?
She's got a lot
on her plate.
She's got school.
She's got work.
This is her work!
Oh, hi, Brian.
I thought you had a busy day
at your legal practice.
(groans) Oh...
Hey, Emily! Yeah, I had
some time between cases.
I thought I'd see
how you were doing.
That's so nice of you!
Let me just put
these bags away
and throw some saltines
in the yard for the kids.
You're disgusting.
Hey, I'm sorry,
but Miss Emily and I
have a connection, which
is totally unexpected.
And by the way,
I actually think she's
doing a pretty good job.
She's teaching you
guys independence.
We're one!
Independence means we die!
Do you like this?
I just got it.
Say you like it, or
she's gonna spend
the rest of the afternoon
out returning that stuff.
Looks great!
Wow, you really
fill these things up.
Hey, do you think maybe you'd
want to hang out sometime?
What, you mean like
a movie or something?
Yeah, or-or maybe lunch?
I had a bad experience last
time I went to the movies.
We're good friends,
aren't we, Milo?
We're best friends, Otis.
No! No!
I reject the premise of this!
Okay, who's ready for
Family Movie Night?
All right, tonight's selection:
Tim Burton's
Alice in Wonderland in 3D.
Now let's all sit down
and take our headache.
Or...
or-or...
we could watch...
The Cove,
The Cove?
Isn't that that
horrible documentary
where they kill
all the fish?
Dolphins, actually.
Well, yeah, but this one
was in the video store
under "Ethan's Picks."
Come on, Peter.
Billy's our guest.
(sighs) All right,
we'll watch The Cove.
(men shouting in Japanese,
splashing and thumping)
Oh, my God!
I don't want to see this!
I know you can't tell this,
but the one who's about
to get her throat cut,
she's sorta hot.
Wh-Wh-What are you doing?
What do you think I'm doing?
You're stoolin'?
What, you gotta
do that in here?
Well, where else am I
supposed to do it?
I can't just do it
on the floor, can I?
You'd be all, like,
"Ooh, who left this coil
of rope on the floor?"
It's very... comes out
very ropey is my point.
But I gotta take a bath.
Go on, then.
We're both men.
Well... all right,
I guess.
There you go!
(hearty laugh)
Look at that!
What is...
Whoa! Solar eclipse.
Blocking the sun.
Do not look directly
at it. (laughs)
Wh-Wha-What the hell?
What're you doin'?
I'm just making
a comment.
Um, need to
know somethin'.
Do you hear the word
"morbidly" a lot?
This is not fair.
O-O-Okay.
And, again, I'm gonna
ask one more question,
and don't take this
the wrong way,
but have you actually
got a penis?
Yes.
Where-where is it?
Where is it?
It's in there.
Are you sure?
So it's like Mr.
Snuffleupagus, is it?
Aw, the hell with this.
Lois, get the ruler,
we're measuring again.
And this time, I decide
where the base is.
So then I'm reading
the funnies,
and right before I get
to the last panel,
Billy blurts out,
he goes, he goes,
"You know, those firemen showed
up to get a cat out of the tree,
but it turns out it's really
Marmaduke up there."
It ruined the whole damn thing!
Peter, in Billy's defense,
the strip is called Marmaduke,
and Marmaduke had not yet
made an appearance.
You probably should've
seen that coming.
I tell ya, he was fun at first,
but now I'm not sure I can take
much more of him living here.
Well, Peter, you've more than
paid back your debt to him.
I mean, what did he do?
He-he got you a hood ornament.
If you ask me,
it's time for him to go.
Yeah, you're right.
Plus, the sooner
we get him out of here,
the sooner I can get back
to my cocaine and dollhouses.
(long, loud snorting noise)
(rings bell)
Dinner is served.
(small excited squeal)
Get out!
(panting)
Stewie, what's going on?
Aren't you supposed
to be at day care?
I escaped.
What happened to your arm?
I finally stood up for all of us
and told Miss Emily we should
be given a proper lunch
and not just what's left over
from her Baja Fresh.
And she said
I shouldn't raise my voice
and pulled me really hard
into the other room,
and my arm came
out of its socket.
Are you sure?
Are you sure you didn't
just sleep on it funny?
Does this look like
I slept on it funny?!
I'm gonna tell Mom!
Mom!
You are not going anywhere.
I finally have a date
with Miss Emily tomorrow,
and I'm not gonna let you
or anybody else get in my way
until I have seen
every inch of her naked.
Do you even hear yourself?!
And what am I supposed
to do about my arm?!
I'll just pop it back in.
You most certainly will not!
I need to go to a hospital.
LOIS: Brian, is Stewie
in there with you?
Mom!
We're in here, Lois.
He's napping.
Relax. I'm gonna
pop it back in.
(muffled grunting)
Get in there! C-Come on!
Hold still, Stewie!
(both grunting)
(shoulder popping)
(coughing)
I'm not saying
I like pain.
But I'm not saying
I don't like it either.
Hey, uh, listen, Billy, it's
been fun having you stay here,
but we really need to talk about
making some new arrangements.
Oh, do we?
Is this because there's
some kind of problem
with the hood ornament?
No, that's... it's...
that's... it's-it's fine.
Oh, good, good.
That's good to hear,
'cause it dawned on me
that the only thing better than
you having one of them would
be you having two of them.
Don't you say those things.
Don't you say those things
unless they're true.
Yeah, be quite a thing
for you to have two of them,
wouldn't it?
Would it ever!
Wonderful!
The best!
Very fancy!
Now, what was it you wanted
to talk to me about?
Nothing, nothing.
(knocking)
Tricia Takanawa?
What are you doing here?
Peter, I'm standing here
on your front porch,
hoping to kill that dolphin
with this harpoon.
MAN (singing):
So the thing about dolphin
lullabies is that they're all
in the key of
"eee-eee"!
(laughing)
"Eee"!
That's loud.
I get why
that's factual.
I don't see
why it's funny.
(laughing)
Eh-eh! What the hell, man?!
Drink beer much?
(laughs)
I just learned that
"much" thing from the telly.
Hey, here's a question:
When are you going
back to the ocean?
Yeah, I mean, don't you have
family back there?
I used to, but not anymore.
Um, the wife won't
have me back.
Threw me out, actually.
Well, maybe you
should talk to her.
Peter, believe me, if she'd take
me back, I'd go in a second.
But she won't, so as much
as I love her, moot point.
Moving on.
Uh... (clears throat)
Well, gotta go
and drain the eel.
It's electric.
(laughing):
My penis.
BILLY:
Hey, throw darts much?
(laughing)
Boy, I see what
you're saying, Peter.
Billy's annoying.
Yeah, and P.S.,
that guy doesn't throw
darts much. He's new.
Peter, I thought you said you
were gonna ask Billy to leave.
He's still sleeping
on the couch out there.
I know, Lois, but I found out
he's only here
'cause his wife kicked him out.
So I figured out a way to kill
two birds with one stone.
(chirping)
Like this.
The key to that, Lois,
is big rock, small birds.
Oh, and I also figured out
how to achieve two goals
with one action.
See, I'm gonna help Billy
get back together with his wife,
and then he'll move out
and stop annoying us.
How do you plan to do that?
Are you kidding?
I'm great at getting
people back together.
I even recorded a song about it.
("Reunited" intro playing)
♪ Reunited
and it feels so good ♪
♪ Doin' someone
that you used to do ♪
♪ That's what
this song's about ♪
♪ You could find someone else
♪ But this
seems a little easier ♪
♪ 'Cause you
already have their number ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah...
Hey, guys.
Everybody having
fun playing with...
What-what is that?
A piece of wood with a,
with a nail in it. Neat.
He can't hear you.
There was a kitchen
explosion today,
and half the kids are deaf.
Oh, hi, Brian.
Hey, Emily.
Wow, you look great.
You're ready to go?
Yeah, one sec.
I'm leaving, honey.
Okay, babe, have fun.
I'm probably just gonna take
a couple more showers.
Who-who was that?
That's my boyfriend, Devin.
Are you ready for lunch?
RADIO DISPATCHER: 11-25,
Code 6, 105 North Avenue...
What you did
to these kids...
There is a special place
in hell for people like you.
Come on, let's go home.
Man, when she
gets to jail,
she's gonna be
major lez-chow.
She sure is, Stewie.
She sure is.
I'm telling you, Peter,
you're wasting your time.
She's never taking me back.
Well, you'll never
know until you try.
Hey, I brought this sack
of garbage from my home.
Where do I put this?
Just anywhere?
Yeah. Anywhere.
Yay, people!
All right, here she comes.
Oh, hello, Joanne.
Billy?! What are
you doing here?
He's here because he loves you,
and he wants to patch things up.
Hey, how come
you ain't got boobs?
You like a runner
or something?
Who's this, then?
He's just a friend,
trying to help.
Look, Billy,
I don't care
what you or your fat friend
here has to say, it's over.
(sighs) Well, thanks
for trying.
I knew she wouldn't
listen to you, though.
Well, maybe so.
But I know someone
she'll have to listen to.
Hey, gang,
I'm Aquaman.
Get back together.
Boop-boop-boop-boop-
boop-boop-boop.
That's not
Aquaman!
Billy, what
is going on?
Let me answer that.
Look, Joanne, Billy had
nothing to do with this.
It was just a dumb plan my
buddies and I put together
because we know how
much Billy loves you.
And he misses you very much.
Look, just give him
another chance.
And if you won't do it
for me, do it for Fish Jesus.
Do you have Fish Jesus?
Of course.
He was nailed to a board
and hung in a man's study
as a novelty to
sing funny songs.
Your god is a gag gift,
did you know that?
Would you excuse us?
Is it true, Billy?
Do you really miss me?
Joanne, I am so sorry.
I promise
I'll do better.
You know what?
I had to live on the land
to learn there might
be a million fish in the sea,
but there's only one you.
Oh, Billy...
Aw, look at that.
That's nice.
Oh, cool, they're
already using my garbage!
Hey, Brian, thanks for helping
get rid of Miss Emily.
Although I've got to say,
my new preschool teacher
is even hotter.
Really?
Yeah.
Let me know if you
want his number.
Oh, you!
Okay, now just
stay like this
and let Peter and Lois
finish their thing.
Wow, Peter, you did
a really nice thing
helping Billy get back
together with his wife.
Yeah, and the best part
is, he's out of the house
and back in the ocean.
I guess everything
worked out for everybody.
Arr! 'Tis a mighty haul!
Hey.
Oh.
Yeah, it's me as Neptune.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru